LOGAN HOSODA

loganhosoda@gmail.com | (509) 964-5926 Spokane Valley, WA 99206

Portfolio | GitHub | LinkedIn

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Seasoned Compounding Specialist with nearly 5 years of experience at Jubilant HollisterStier, meeting company goals utilizing consistent and organized practices. Skilled in working under pressure and adapting to new situations and challenges to meet expectations. Full stack developer that is quick to learn, well versed in technology, eager to learn new tech stacks, and overcome new challenges.

PROJECTS

- O Please visit my **portfolio** for a detailed description of each project.
 - Front-End Work Assessment | GitHub Repo
 - Ruby Backend Work Assessment | GitHub Repo
 - Copycat Iphone Calculator | GitHub Repo | Live
 - Etch A Sketch | GitHub Repo | Live
 - Tic Tac Toe | GitHub Repo | Live

CERTIFICATIONS

[Accelerated Computer Science Fundamentals Specialization] - Coursera, University of Illinois - Issued Jan 2022

[Unordered Data Structures] - Coursera, University of Illinois - Issued Jan 2022 **[Ordered Data Structures]** - Coursera, University of Illinois - Issued Dec 2021 **[Object Oriented Data Structures In C++]** - Coursera, University of Illinois - Issued Nov 2021

[Certified Trainer] - Jubilant HollisterStier, Spokane - Issued Apr 2019

SKILLS

 \bigcirc

- Ruby, Ruby on Rails
- Javascript, React
- Front-End Skills: HTML5, CSS3
- Back-End and Database Skills
- REST, APIs, JSON
- SQL, PostgreSQL

- C++
- Object Oriented Programming
- Data Structures, Algorithms
- Version Control Systems: Git, GitHub
- Operating Systems: Linux, Windows, Mac

WORK HISTORY

Compounding Specialist | Jubilant HollisterStier - Spokane, WA

11/2020 - Current

- Managed 3rd shift compounding team, meeting production requirements daily given available manpower
- First line of contact regarding problems, or setbacks requiring path forward. Used critical thinking to evaluate solutions, made effective decisions
- Maintained strong communication with neighboring departments and leadership, ensuring all parties are well informed, equipped with accurate information and timeframes
- Reviewed batch records, and manufacturing process procedures. Ensuring procedures are easy to follow, and handwritten entries are error free

Process Tech IV, Compounding | Jubilant HollisterStier - Spokane, WA

04/2018 - 11/2020

- Trained to manufacture over 20 different compounds across two separate manufacturing lines
- Trained new hires to utilize compounding equipment, and follow procedures to manufacture several compounds
- Worked closely with the compounding team to manufacture bulk pharmaceutical drug substances. Governed by the FDA, followed strict timelines and instructions to perform job functions
- Maintained strong aseptic technique to fulfill requirements to work within ISO classified cleanrooms

Process Tech II, Packaging | US Tech Solutions - Spokane, WA

11/2017 - 04/2018

- Trained to detect defects in vials filled with pharmaceutical drug substances via hand inspection methods, and semi-automatic inspection, allowing for inspection of up to 100 vials per minute
- Labeled and packaged vials. Ensured vials were labeled properly without any issues, while also ensuring that packaging was in great, presentable condition
- Followed Good Documentation Practice (GDP), ensuring excellent documentation on contract batch records, which includes clear/legible handwritten entries, without error, documented in real time
- Temporary position, contracted to work at Jubilant HollisterStier

EDUCATION

Five Mile Prairie School - Spokane, WA
High School Diploma
2008 - 2014

Spokane Community College - Spokane, WA 2013 - 2013

Mt. Spokane High School - Mead, WA 2013 - 2014